+1 612-229-7062 | antonioraquel@outlook.com

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced administrative and operations manager with broad capabilities in Information Technology acquisition, installation, training and servicing; Azure AD, PaperCut, Provide, Microsoft Defender Security & Compliance, ATP, EDR, Intune, SSO and MFA experienced, Networking and Cloud Security; facilities management; office administration, budgeting and contract negotiation; client relations and social service case management; and, personnel recruitment, training and leadership. Focus on Cybersecurity in the nonprofit world.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# 2016 - Present Technology and Operations Manager

# Rainbow Health Responsibilities and Accomplishments:

2577 Territorial Rd, Saint Paul, MN

- Reporting to the CEO, managed, supervised and conducted all functions relating to Information Technology (IT), facilities management and office administration.
- Regularly assessed organizational IT needs, and managed many highly successful IT acquisitions and installations, including formal training and ongoing support for all IT users.
- Transition from on-premises fileshares to Sharepoint sites. Agency-wide MS Teams deployment and training at the start of mandatory remote work.
- Microsoft Defender ATP configuration and deployment, worked with a team in deploying SentinelOne EDR, bringing the agency into Cyber Insurance compliance.
- Azure MFA and SSO deployment on all compatible web applications.
- Achieved significant IT vendor cost savings with negotiated contract service agreements.
- Developed and administered numerous RFP's and subsequent service and equipment contracts.
- Supervised the remodel of a new leased facility and the buildout of a new 5,000 sq. ft. clinic.
- Successfully maintained and ensured accuracy of staff data records and compliance with all employment laws and regulations.
- Proactively recruited, screened, and selected candidates to support current and future resource requirements; oriented
  new hires to insure a positive and productive employment experience; and, supervised direct reports and ensured each
  employee had a clear and thorough understanding of their role and responsibilities.

## 2015 – 2016 Housing Specialist | Transitional Housing Program – Ryan White

## **Minnesota AIDS Project**

1400 Park Avenue S, Minneapolis, MN

# Responsibilities and Accomplishments:

- Worked directly with clients to provide housing to HIV-positive persons, who met eligibility criteria, to decrease the risk of homelessness for clients and to assist clients in obtaining transitional and long-term housing solutions.
- Successfully maintained a case load of 8 to 12 formerly homeless clients, working to provide clients with housing resources; assisted in housing search, landlord negotiations.
- Conducted numerous initial and ongoing client assessments to determine eligibility and to address housing needs.
- Successfully built and maintained client relationships based on respect, trust and healthy boundaries.
- Maintained accurate statistical information and documentation to ensure continuity of service and meet agency and contract requirements.

## 2014 - 2016 Administrative Assistant to Director of Finance and Human Resources

# Minnesota AIDS Project

1400 Park Avenue S, Minneapolis, MN

#### Responsibilities and Accomplishments:

- Provided administrative and operations support in Operations and Human Resources.
- Successfully served as primary contact for Managed IT services and troubleshooting.
- Coordinated and supervised building maintenance and managed outside contractors and vendors.
- Cost-effectively maintained office equipment and organizational supplies inventory.
- Managed reception area staff and monitored building safety and security.
- Collected and analysed gift, donation and grant data using Salesforce and Raiser's Edge.
- Supported the Mainline/Syringe Exchange program by providing clean syringes, safe disposal of used paraphernalia and counselling on best practices.

## Projectionist (5 years)

# **UCI - Paramount/Universal Studios**

Portugal (European Union)

- Trained in handling and maintenance of Cinemeccanica Victoria 5 cinema projector.
- Soundstage training with Dolby Digital DPC-80.
- Programming of automation systems in support of Cinemeccanica V5.
- Training on best practices in replacing Xenon arc bulbs and maintenance of projector platters.
- Film reel inspection and splicing for premiers.

#### Computer and Network Technician (1 year)

#### **Prologica**

Portugal (European Union)

- Assisted with planning and deployment of Network Infrastructure.
- Applied computer and repair skills including hardware repairs and installation including drivers, video and sound, memory upgrades, motherboard and PSU replacement.
- Managed operating system and software installation, management and maintenance.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

2000

Arts & Design

ESRDL | Portugal (European Union)

#### **CERTIFICATES**

- Cybersecurity [University of Minnesota]
- Narcan Administration
- Mental Health First Aid
- HIPAA/HITECH Compliance for Healthcare Professionals
- OSHA Compliance
- First Aid/CPR
- Boundaries in Supervision
- Intent versus Impact: Understanding Microaggressions
- Implicit Bias in Public Health Practice

## **PERSONAL SKILLS**

LANGUAGES Fluent in Portuguese, English and conversational Spanish (Galego)

#### **SKILLS**

- Advanced level of MS Windows environment, administration and hardening
- Intermediate knowledge of Intune & Autopilot, Active Directory, Azure AD, MS Defender Security (ATP)
- Knowledge of Wireshark, SIEMS (Splunk), Nessus, Networking and Cloud Security
- Strong grasp of MS Office, MS Teams, Zoom, Slack
- Digital Art and Design Software experience (Adobe Photoshop)
- Computer repair skills include hardware repairs and installation, including drivers, video and sound, memory upgrades, motherboard and PSU replacement
- Basic knowledge of Linux (Debian) and Mac OSX
- Knowledge of Salesforce, Raiser's Edge and EveryAction
- Intermediate knowledge of ADP payroll systems
- Papercut